【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
丑裸男在装饰圣诞树
Ugly Naked Guy is decorating his tree.
天啊 你们该来看看 他的圣诞球有多大
Oh my God! You should see the size of his Christmas balls!
嘿      嘿
Hey.        Hey.
你们今年给了管理员多少钱的红包
How much did you guys tip the super this year?
我们打算给50
Yeah, we were gonna give fifty.
但是如果你们给的比这多的话 我们也不想太难堪
But if you guys gave more, we don't wanna look bad.
事实上 今年我们只送了他一些自制的曲奇
Oh, actually this year we just made him homemade cookies.
那就给25
And twenty-five it is.
你们送他曲奇
You gave him cookies?
钱太没人情味了      对
Money is so impersonal.        Yeah.
曲奇能表示关心他们
Cookies says someone really cares.
好吧 我们破产了 但曲奇的确表达那层意思
All right, we're broke, but cookies do say that.
我了解
I can see that.
有盘布朗尼曾经给我念过打油诗
A plate of brownies once told me a limerick.
菲比 我问你 那些布朗尼是不是很搞笑
Pheebs, let me ask you something. Were these "funny" brownies?
也一般吧
Not especially.
不过 我觉得里面有大麻
But, you know, I think they had pot in them.
两位 你们还送过谁曲奇作红包
So you guys, who else did you tip with cookies?
邮差 管理员
The mailman, the super...
还有那个送报纸的
Oh and the newspaper delivery guy.
天啊
Oh my God!
怎么了
What?
我想 你们不会喜欢这个的
I don't think you're gonna like this.
天啊
Oh gosh!
这是压烂在体育版里的碎曲奇
Oh, these are cookies smashed in the Sports section.
看 他还玩了我的字谜游戏
Oh look, and he did my crossword puzzle.
而且还错漏百出
Yeah, but not very well,
除了横14的"盖西文音乐剧"
Unless 14 across "Gershwin musical"
是"去死吧 去死吧 去死吧"
actually is "Bite me, bite me. bite me."
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第09集
菲比的爸爸 The One With Phoebe's Dad
调校制作：海盗美剧 寒 枫
字幕编辑：海盗美剧 小龟快快跑
我不敢相信圣诞节已经到了
I can't believe it's Christmas already, you know?
才刚吃过感恩节火鸡 转眼间
I mean, one day you're eating turkey, the next thing you know
神在跳舞 鹅在下蛋 (一首圣诞颂歌的歌词)
your lords are a-leaping and your geese are a-laying.
所以每年的这个时候 鹅都很轻松
Which is why geese are so relaxed this time of year.
大家好      嘿
Hey, guys.        Hey.
嘿 瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
我买了个小礼物送给你
I got you a little present.
我来拆
I'll open it.
这是弹簧圈
It's a Slinky!
记得吗
Remember, huh?
滚下楼 不论一个或两个
Walks downstairs alone or in pairs,
大家都知道 它是一个大弹簧
Everyone knows it's just a big spring.
你还在生我的气 就因为
You're still mad because of the whole...
那张 不想跟我在一起的理由 可恶的清单
Horrible and degrading list of reasons not to be with me?
从现在起 我们称那为 “不幸的插曲” 怎么样？
How about for now we just call it "the unfortunate incident"?
阿甘 你住的地方有楼梯吗
Hey Gunther, you got stairs in your place?
有啊      给你玩吧
Yeah.         Go nuts.
大家好      嘿
Hey, guys.        Hey.
袋子里是什么东西
What's in the bag?
只是一些礼物
Just some presents.
来吧 让我们看看你买了什么
Come on, show us what you bought.
少装啦
You know you want to.
好吧
Okay.
这是以小本的名义 送我父母的相框
Okay! This is a picture frame from Ben to my parents.
好可爱
Oh, that's cute.
这是送给苏珊及卡萝儿的女女毛巾
I got some "Hers" and "Hers" towels for Susan and Carol.
我买了这件上衣送给老妈
And I got this blouse for Mom.
罗斯 这太漂亮了      是吗
Ross, that is gorgeous!         Yeah?
看看这些逼真的假勋章
Look at these authentic fake medals!
我跟你说 妈妈肯定会被选为
I tell you, Mom's gonna be voted "best dressed"
古怪军校的最佳着装
at the make believe military academy!
嘿      嘿
Hey.         Hey.
平安夜前夜快乐      你也是
Happy Christmas Eve Eve.         You too.
天啊 这是哪儿来的
Oh my God! Where did you get this?
梅西百货三楼 家饰部
Macy's, third floor, home furnishings.
他是我爸
This is my father!
这是我爸的照片
This is a picture of my dad!
菲比 那是相框里附送的照片
Pheebs, that's the guy that comes in the frame.
不 才不是呢 他是我爸 我证明给你们看
No, it isn't. This is my dad. Alright, I'll show you.
菲比 我以为你爸在坐牢
Phoebe, I thought your dad was in prison.
那是我的继父
No, that's my stepdad.
我生父在我出生前就抛弃了我们
My real dad's the one that ran out on us before I was born.
你怎么从未上过奥普拉的节目
How have you never been on Oprah?
看吧 就是他
Okay look! See? This is him.
我妈去世前给了我这张照片 是同一个人
My mother gave me this picture before she died. Same guy!
亲爱的 这是一张相框模特儿
Honey, this is a picture of the frame guy
跟一只牧羊犬 在浅蓝色的布景前面拍的照
posing in front of a bright blue screen with a collie.
那不是蓝色布景 那是
It's not a blue screen. It's just...
或许那天的天气很好
Maybe it was just really clear that day.
好吧 我得找我外婆谈一谈
Okay, I have to talk to my grandmother.
等一下 亲爱的      菲比
Wait a minute, honey!        Pheebs.
我试着勾引我老板的前妻跟我上床
So anyway, I'm trying to get my boss's exwife to sleep with me.
乔伊
Joey.
菲比有问题时 大家都愿意听
Oh, but when Phoebe has a problem, everyone's all ears!
艾瑟林文斯
Esther Livingston.
死了
Gone!
嘿 小菲
Hi Pooh.
外婆 你在做什么
Hi Gram. What're you doing?
更新电话簿
Oh! Just updating the phone book.
外婆
Gram?
我能再看一下我爸的照片吗
Can I see the pictures of my dad again?
哦
Oh!
没问题 当然可以
Oh sure, sure.
怎么了
How come?
我只是想看看他
Just, you know, to see him.
没问题 在这儿
Oh, sure. Here.
好
All right.
这是你爸站在草地上
This is the one of your father in a meadow.
教一个小男孩放风筝
And, helping a little boy fly a kite.
这是他参加毕业典礼
And here he is at a graduation.
另一场毕业典礼
Another graduation.
他真的是我父亲吗
Okay. Is this really my father?
他真的是你父亲
Is it really your...
当然是的
Well, of course it is.
我闻到烟味了 因为有人要火烧屁股了
I smell smoke. Maybe that's because someone's pants are on fire!
我
Well I...
我们祖孙这么多年
Y'know, in all the years we've been grandmother and granddaughter
你从来没对我说过谎
you have never lied to me.
好吧 他不是你爸 只是相框附送的照片
All right, that's not your father. That's just a picture of a guy in a frame.
天啊
Oh God!
那是你妈的点子
It was your mother's idea.
她不要你知道你生父是谁
Y'know, she didn't want you to know your real father.
因为他离开时 她真的很伤心
Because it hurt her so much when he left.
我本来也不想跟着她骗你
I didn't wanna go along with it.
但她死了 我很难跟她争论
But then she died and it was harder to argue with her.
不是不可能 但是更难了
Not impossible, but harder.
好吧 那他不是著名的树医生
All right. So was he not a famous tree surgeon?
而且我猜 他也不住在 没有电话的缅甸茅屋里头
And then I guess, okay, he doesn't live in a hut in Burma where there's no phones?
据我所知 他在州北部的某个地方当药剂师
Last I heard, he was a pharmacist somewhere upstate.
那一点道理都没有
Okay. That makes no sense.
为什么村民要崇拜一个药剂师
Why would the villagers worship a pharmacist?
亲爱的
Honey...
喔 对      对
Oh. Yeah.        Yeah.
总之 我只知道那么多
Anyway, that's all I know.
那个
That
还有这个
and this.
这是
This
真正的他
is the real him.
噢
Oh!
我记得我爸 穿着一身红色的衣服
Y'know, I remember my father all dressed up in the red suit,
黑色大靴子 还有漆皮皮带
the big black boots and the patent leather belt,
在楼下鬼鬼祟祟
sneaking around downstairs.
他不想我们看到他
He didn't want anybody to see him.
但是他又喝醉了
But he'd be drunk.
走路摇摇晃晃 撞上东西 把大家都吵醒了
So he'd stumble, crash into something and wake everybody up.
听起来 不像是个快乐的圣诞节
Well, that doesn't sound like a very merry Christmas.
谁说是圣诞节来着
Who said anything about Christmas?
嗨
Hi!
嘿 谁有菲比的消息
Hey, anyone hear from Phoebe yet?
没有 完全没消息
No, nothing.
希望她没事
I hope she's okay.
我能了解她的感受
Yeah. I know exactly what she's going through.
你怎么会完全了解她的感受
How do you know exactly what she's going through?
她跟我们说了
She told us.
你买了什么 摩妮卡
So what do you got there, Monica?
派对要用的东西
Just stuff for the party.
你们还在这里干嘛
Yeah, what're you guys doing here?
你们不是应该去血拼的吗
Aren't you guys supposed to be shopping?
你们还没有买礼物吗
You guys haven't gotten your presents yet?
明天就是平安夜 你们打算怎么办
Tomorrow's Christmas Eve! What are you gonna do?
不是只有粘土动画里的人才会这么说话吗
Don't you have to be Claymation to say stuff like that?
对了 摩妮卡 我想邮差不喜欢你的曲奇
Oh, by the way, Mon, I don't think the mailman liked your cookies.
这是你妈寄来的装饰品
Here are the ornaments your mom sent.
好吧
Well.
或许邮差喜欢曲奇
Maybe the mailman liked the cookies.
只是我们给的不够
We just didn't give him enough.
摩妮卡 鸽子都比你聪明
Monica, pigeons learn faster than you.
嘿 瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
我想我知道 怎么做能让你开心一点
You know what? I think I know what will make you feel better.
你也列一张关于我的清单 怎么样
How about you make a list about me?
什么 算了 罗斯 不要
Wha... forget it, Ross, no.
我才不要站在这里列清单
I am not gonna stand here and make a list of ...
好吧 你爱抱怨
Okay, youre whiny.
你偏执 没有安全感
You are obsessive. You are insecure.
非常没胆
You're gutless.
你无法把握机会
You know, you don't ever, you don't just sort of seize the day, you know?
你喜欢我一整年 却没采取任何行动
You like me for what, a year, you didn't do anything about it.
还有 你的发胶抹太多了
And... Oh you wear too much of that gel in your hair.
看吧 你
See, there. You...
你照我的话去做了
All right, you did what I said.
没错 你知道吗 你说的对 我真的感觉好多了
Yeah, and you know what? You're right. I do feel better.
谢谢你 罗斯
Thank you, Ross.
对 在奥巴尼 能告诉我法兰克布非的电话吗
Yeah, in Albany. Could I have the number of Frank Buffay?
好的 伊夕卡呢
Okay, in Ithaca?
好吧 沙拉托加呢
All right, Saratoga?
奥尼昂坦呢
Oneonta?
你知道吗 你不该自称是查号台
You know what? You shouldn't call yourself information!
嘿
Hey.
外婆 如果那是你的真名
Hello, Grandma. If that is in fact your real name.
别这样 小菲 别再生我的气了
Come on. Now, Pooh, don't still be mad at me.
怎么样      没结果
How's it going?         Oh, not so good.
州北部很大 他很渺小 你自己想吧
Upstate's pretty big. He's pretty small. You do the math.
我想 没有他 你能过得更好
Well, I think you're better off without him.
亲爱的 我知道他是你爸
Oh honey, I know he's your daddy.
但对我来说 他仍是那个不负责的混蛋
But to me, he's still the irresponsible creep
搞大你妈的肚子 偷走她的小魔怪玩具
who knocked up your mom and stole her Gremlin.
我了解 我只想知道他是谁
I know. I just wanted to know who he was, you know?
对 我知道
Yeah. I know.
好吧
Okay.
其实我没有完全说实话
I wasn't completely honest with you
我跟你说我不知道他在哪里
when I told you that I didn't know exactly where he lived.
什么意思
What do you mean?
他住在米德尔敦月桂路74号
He lives at 74 Laurel Drive in Middletown.
看到乳制品女王 就代表你走过了
If you hit the Dairy Queen, you've gone too far.
你可以开我的出租车去
You can take my cab.
哇
Wow!
谢谢
Thank you.
不能让其他人开那辆出租车
Now, remember nobody else drives that cab.
我知道 我要去见我爸了
Got it. Oh! I'm gonna see my dad!
谢谢
Thank you!
好吧 祝我好运吧 外公
Okay. Oh! Wish me luck, Grandpa.
嘿
Hey.
菲比把出租车开过来了吗
Phoebe here with the cab yet?
对 她开了辆隐形出租车
Yeah, she brought the invisible cab.
上车吧
Hop in!
她最好快一点 商店七点就关门了
She'd better get here soon. The outlet stores close at 7.
别担心 开车到菲比爸家要两小时
Hey, don't worry. I figure it'll  be two hours to Phoebe's dad's house.
他们会见面 聊天 分享人生故事
They'll meet, they'll chat, they'll swap life stories.
我们仍然有的是时间
We'll still have plenty of time.
她来了      嘿
Hey, here she comes!         Hey.
嘿
Hey, hey.
嗨
Hi.
嘿      嘿
Hey.        Hey.
你们能相信吗
Can you believe this?
两小时后 我就有爸爸了
In like two hours I'm gonna have a dad.
没错 重大事件哦
Yeah, big stuff.
好吧 我们出发吧      好的
Okay, let's go.         Okay.
拿去 这个给你      好的
Here, you have to hold this.         Okay.
煞车左边 油门右边
Brake, left. Gas, right?
那是我的小抄
Yeah, that's my cheat sheet.
我的安全带在哪里
Where's my seat belt?
那边没有安全带
Oh, no no, that side doesn't have one.
被救护人员剪开了
The paramedics had to cut through it.
嘿      嘿
Hey.         Hey.
来吧 快告诉我 拜托
Come on, just tell me. Please, please.
这是第16次 不 我不觉得你偏执
For the 16th time, no, I do not think you're obsessive.
天啊 这里真的好热
Oh gosh. It's hot in here!
瑞秋 关掉暖气
Rach, get the heat.
罗斯 请你关掉暖气      没问题
Ross, turn the heat down, please?         Sure.
它们之间有明显的差别 偏执和
By the way, there's a difference between being obsessive...
罗斯 暖气
Ross, the heat!
好吧 暖气 暖气 暖气 还说我偏执
Fine. Okay. Heat heat heat. And I'm the obsessive one?
好的
Okay.
这边是开
This way is on.
所以这边是
So this is...
关
off.
你把散热器弄坏了
Did you just break the radiator?
不 我只是转一下开关 然后
No, no, I was turning the knob and...
就变成这样了
Here it is.
把它装回去
Well, put it back!
它
It...
装不回去
It won't go back.
我打电话给管理员
I'll call the super.
来吧 让我试试看
Here, let me try.
没错 我忘了你有熔化金属的超能力
Oh oh, that's right. I forgot about your ability to fuse metal.
好笑的远亲
Hey, it's Funny's cousin,
不好笑
Not Funny!
崔格先生
Hi, Mr. Treeger?
我是楼上的瑞秋葛林
It's Rachel Green from upstairs.
对 有人弄坏了我们的暖气开关
Yes, somebody broke our knob on the radiator.
这里真的很热
And it's really hot in here.
对 热到可以烤曲奇了
Yes, it's hot enough to bake cookies.
你能在六点前帮我们换新的吗
Well, do you think we could have a new one by six?
什么 不 星期二 我们不能等到星期二
What? No, no. Tuesday? We can't wait until Tuesday.
今晚我们要举行派对
We're having a party tonight.
好吧 给他红包
Okay, tip the man.
不 如果他不喜欢我们的曲奇 太可惜了
No. If he doesn't like our cookies, too bad.
我才不要被勒索
I won't be blackmailed.
就算情况变糟 变得有点热
Look if worse comes to worse, it gets a little warm,
我们可以办主题派对
We'll call it a theme party.
派对主题 "请进 热锅上的蚂蚁"
Hey, here's a theme, "Come on in, live like bacon!"
我们到了
Ooh. this is it.
74号
Seventy four.
原来这个的功用是那样啊
Oh. so, that's what this is for!
就是这里 我要见到我爸了
This is it. I'm gonna meet my dad.
这真的很重大 对吧
This is like the biggest thing ever, huh?
对      当然
Yeah.         Sure is.
好吧 我要进去了
Okay, here I go. I'm going in.
好的
All right!
祝你好运 菲比
Good luck, Pheebs.
好的
Okay.
我要进去了
Here I go.
我要去了
I'm going.
嗨
Hi.
欢迎光临我们的热带圣诞节派对
Welcome to our tropical Christmas party.
可以将外套 毛衣 裤子 跟衬衫 放到卧室里
You can put your coats and sweaters and pants and shirts in the bedroom.
很难看得出来 因为我在流汗
It's hard to tell because I'm sweating.
但我完全是按照 发胶瓶身说明使用的
But I use exactly what the gel bottle says.
一颗豆子大小的份量而已
An amount about the size of a pea.
那怎么会太多呢
How can that be too much?
冰块
Ice?
冰块 谁要冰块 拿张纸巾
Ice? Ice squares anyone? Take a napkin.
好吧
All right.
摩妮卡 摩妮卡
Monica? Monica!
摩妮卡 你的客人快变成肉干了
Monica, your guests are turning into jerky. Okay？
是吗 我觉得蛮舒服的
Really? I'm perfectly comfortable.
嘿 嘿 嘿 排队 老兄 我是下一个
Hey, hey, hey, get in line buddy, I was next.
崔格先生
Mr. Treeger.
你说你们要办派对
You said there was a party.
没错
Oh, yeah！
欢迎光临我们的三温暖
Well, hey, welcome to our sauna.
很热吗 我从来不觉得热
Is it hot? My body always stays cool.
或许是因为我的皮很厚
Probably because I have so much skin.
嘿 芝士
Hey, cheese!
好了 这是个机会 摩妮卡 给他现金
Alright, alright, here's the chance. Monica, give him cash.
瑞秋 把你的耳环送给他 想想办法 什么都可以
Rachel, give him your earrings. Something, now, anything!
不 我不会屈服的
No. I will not cave.
我支持摩妮卡
Yeah, I'm with Mon.
好吧 好吧 你说我不懂得把握机会
Alright, alright, you know how you say I never seize the day?
好吧 尽管他是你们的管理员 我也要把握机会
Well, alright, even though he's your super, I'm seizing.
崔格先生
Mr. Treeger?
这是五十块 圣诞快乐
Here is fifty bucks. Merry Christmas!
哇
Oh wow!
我没给你准备礼物
I didn't get you anything.
给你五块
Here's five back.
不 那是你的圣诞节红包
No no, no, that, that's your Christmas tip, alright?
对了 你认为你可不可以 现在把暖气给修好
Oh, hey, do you think there's a chance you could fix that radiator now?
不行 我跟女孩们说过
No can do. Like I told the girl.
星期二才能拿到开关零件
I can't get a knob until Tuesday.
罗斯      什么
Ross?        Yeah?
看样子 他在打棒球
Looks like he's playing baseball.
你是说 他在玩硬的吗
You mean hardball?
都一样
Whatever.
你要怎么办
What you gonna do?
失陪 我要去把握机会
Excuse me. I'm seizing.
崔格先生
Mr. Treeger?
再给你五十
Here's another fifty.
光明节快乐
Happy Hanukkah.
这能帮助你快点拿到开关零件吗
Will, will this help with the knob getting?
不行
No.
商店星期二才会开门
The place is not open till Tuesday.
我说的还不够清楚吗
Am I not saying it right?
这么说 你真的喜欢我的曲奇
So, wait, you really did like my cookies?
当然 非常有感情 证明你们真的关心我
Oh yeah, they were so personal. It really showed you cared.
你太会把握机会了 发胶男孩
Nice seizing, gel boy.
这是槲寄生吗
So, is this mistletoe?
不 那是 那是罗勒
No, no, that, that is basil.
如果那是槲寄生 我就要亲你了
If it was mistletoe, I was gonna kiss you.
不 那是罗勒
Yeah, no, it's still basil.
好吧
Okay.
你跑到哪里了      信箱
How far did you get?         Mailbox.
好吧 我们有进步了
All right, we're getting closer.
菲比 到底怎么了
What's going on?
其实是所有的事情混在一起
No, it's just like, you know, it's a whole mess of stuff, you know.
比如说 昨天我爸是著名的缅甸树医生
Because like yesterday, you know, my dad was this famous Burma tree surgeon guy.
现在他是药剂师
And, you know, now he's a pharmacist guy and...
或许他是很酷的药剂师
Well, maybe he's this really cool pharmacist guy.
没错 或许他是 我去敲门
Yeah, maybe, yeah. You know, and, and I'll knock on the door.
他会拥抱我 我就有爸爸了
And he'll hug me, and I'll have a dad.
我会去他的药房
Ya know and I'll, I'll go to his pharmacy.
大家都会对我好
And everyone will be nice to me.
因为我是法兰克的女儿
Because, you know, I'm Frank's daughter.
那为什么你不去敲门呢
So why not go knock?
因为如果他不是个好爸爸呢
Well, 'cause, I mean, what if, what if he's not this great dad guy?
我是说 如果他还是那个
I mean, what if, what if he's just still the dirtbag
抛弃我妈跟我们的混蛋呢
who ran out on my mom and us?
对      嗯
Yeah.        Hmm.
你们知道吗
You know what?
这星期我已经失去了一个假爸爸
I've already lost a fake dad this week and...
我不想再失去一个真爸爸
I don't think I'm ready to lose a real one.
菲比 没关系的 今天你跨出了一大步
Pheebs, that's okay. You took a big step today.
是吗      对
Yeah?        Yeah.
有一天  当你准备好时 就会越过那片篱笆了
And someday, when you're ready, you'll make it past the hedges.
没错 那个时候 他会有幸得到你这样的女儿
Yeah! And when you do, he'll be lucky to have you.
你们
You guys...
抱歉 你们来不及去买东西了
I'm sorry about your shopping.
没关系 会有办法的
Oh, that's okay. We'll figure something out.
我知道你不打算进去
Listen Phoebs, I know you're not going in there.
但是你觉得 我能不能去借用一下 他家的洗手间
But do you think it'd be alright if I went in and used his bathroom?
没关系 算了
That's fine, never mind.
酷 下雪了
Cool. Snow!
就像一张空白画布
Kinda like a blank canvas.
天啊 这里好热啊
Ho, ho, ho, holy crap, is it hot in here!
真的好热 介意我把暖气关小点吗
Really, hey, you mind if I turn the heat down?
对呀 我们该早点想到那一点的
Hey, we could have used that kind of thinking earlier!
菲比 怎么样
So, Pheebs, how did it go?
我没办法进去
Oh! I couldn't go in.
亲爱的 我很遗憾      你还好吧
Honey, I'm sorry.         Are you okay?
没事 因为我知道他在那里
Yeah, yeah, no it's okay. Because, I mean, I know he's there.
目前那就已经足够了
So that's enough for now.
嘿 已经过了午夜
Hey, guys, it's after midnight!
祝大家圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas, everyone!
对 圣诞快乐
Oh right! Merry Christmas!
嘿 摩妮卡 开关坏了
Hey, Monica, the knob was broken.
我就从下面把暖气整个关掉 希望别出什么问题
So I just turned it off from underneath. I hope that's alright.
瑞秋 这是给你的
Rach, these are for you.
雨刷
Wiper blades.
可是我连车都没有
I don't even have a car.
没错 有了这个新汽车芳香剂 你会以为自己真有车
No, but with this newcar smell, you'll think you do.
好吧 菲比 轮到你了
Okay, Pheebs, your turn.
马桶座垫纸
Toiletseat covers.
你们趁我去加油时买的吗
Is that what you were doing while I was getting gas?
你们太贴心了
You guys!
给罗斯的礼物
And for Ross
爱吃甜食的家伙
Mr. Sweet Tooth.
你们送我一罐可乐
You got me a cola drink?
还有一罐柠檬饮料
And a lemonlime!
真是厚礼呀
Well this, this is too much.
我觉得我该再送你一件毛衣
I feel like I should get you another sweater.
最后送出但不是最轻的礼物
And last but not least
螺纹的 让你更有快感
They're ribbed for your pleasure.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧